Guide to the Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
- Series II: Confessions I-N
  - Names: N
    - Nguyen Vann Soi, 2/3/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 49)
    - Nguyen Vann Tev (Teu), N/A (Reel 187, Frame 2)
    - NguyeΣn (Nguyen) Van Sroy, 3/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 34)
    - NguyeΣn ((Nguyen)) Yi Diep, 4/7/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 51)
    - Ngy Navy Neng, 24/12/1977 (Reel 84, Frame 20)
    - Nharay Plen, 6/4/1978 (Reel 84, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/4/1978
    - Nhe Chin Kry, 6/6/1977 (Reel 88, Frame 42)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/6/1978
    - Nhean Chea, 12/6/1977 (Reel 87, Frame 9)
    - Nhean Chong, 1/11/1977 (Reel 88, Frame 18)
    - Nhean Kat, N/A (Reel 82, Frame 2)
    - Nhean Tha, 8/1/1977 (Reel 89, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/2/1977; 6/2/1977; 6/2/1977; 2 sections undated
    - Nheap Phal, N/A (Reel 81, Frame 14)
    - Nhek Ang Kear, 10/1975 (Reel 84, Frame 27)
    - Nhek Chhat, N/A (Reel 89, Frame 16)
    - Nhek Hang, 8/2/1977 (Reel 82, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/8/1977; 23/2/1977; 25/2/1977
    - Nhek Keun, N/A (Reel 88, Frame 34)
    - Nhek Norin, N/A (Reel 85, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/11/1976; 12/11/1976; 5/12/1976; 8/12/1976(2); 24/11/1976; 22/11/1976; 21/11/1976; 14/11/1976; 25/11/1976; 27/11/1976
      20/11/1976(3); 17/11/1976; 16/11/1976(2); 15/11/1976(2); 23/11/1976(2)
      26/11/1976(2); 28/11/1976(2); 30/11/1976(2); 1/12/1976(2); 2/12/1976(3); 3/12/1976(4)
    - Nhek Sann, N/A (Reel 88, Frame 37)
    - Nhek Saroeurn, 5/1/1976 (Reel 88, Frame 22)
    - Nhek Va, N/A (Reel 85, Frame 6)
    - Nhek Veng Huos, 21/8/1976 (Reel 82, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/8/1976; 23/8/1976; 24/8/1976; 23/8/1976; 26/8/1976; 31/8/1976(3); 4/9/1976; 13/8/1976(2)
    - Nhel Him, N/A (Reel 82, Frame 3)
    - Nhel Leap, 1/1/1978 (Reel 87, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/3/1978; 28/2/1978
    - Nhel Sabath, 16/3/1977 (Reel 86, Frame 17)
    - Nhem Cheang, N/A (Reel 88, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/10/1976; 3/11/1976; 10/11/1976; 12/11/1976; 16/11/1976; 19/11/1976; 23/11/1976; 29/11/1976; 3/12/1976; 10/12/1976
    - Nhem Im, N/A (Reel 87, Frame 24)
    - Nhem Kak, 23/9/1977 (Reel 85, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/10/1977
    - Nhem Nan, 28/12/1977 (Reel 88, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/1/1978; 29/1/1978
    - Nhem Nen, 18/10/1976 (Reel 83, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/12/1976; 7/10/1976; 3/12/1976; 29/11/1976; 26/11/1976; 2/11/1976; 21/11/1976; 17/11/1976; 18/11/1976; 14/11/1976; 13/11/1976
      11/11/1976; 8/11/1976; 29/10/1976; 26/10/1976; 24/10/1976; 26/10/1976
      22/12/1976; 27/12/1976
    - Nhem Noeurn, N/A (Reel 83, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/3/1977; 4/4/1977; 17/4/1977; 21/4/1977; 4/5/1977; 6/5/1977
    - Nhem Pho, N/A (Reel 86, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/4/1977; 18/7/1977; 24/3/1977(2); 7/6/1977; 1/4/1977(2); 18/2/1977; 19/3/1977; 8/3/1977; 19/3/1977; 3 sections undated
    - Nhem San, 11/1976 (Reel 87, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/2/1977; 14/3/1977; 15/11/1976
    - Nhem Soeurn, N/A (Reel 83, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/10/1975; 11/10/1975; 15/10/1975; 4 sections undated
    - Nhem Sophat, 30/9/1978 (Reel 83, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/10/1978
    - Nhem Thay, 14/7/1978 (Reel 87, Frame 33)
    - Nhem Yim, N/A (Reel 85, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/8/1977; 20/11/1977
    - Nhen Vann, 16/5/1978 (Reel 88, Frame 44)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/5/78
    - Nhep Boeun, 18/2/1977 (Reel 88, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/4/1977; 1 section undated
    - Nhep Dim, N/A (Reel 88, Frame 4)
    - Nhep Nuch, N/A (Reel 83, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/11/1976; 19/11/1976; 23/11/1976; 25/11/1976; 24/11/1976; 26/11/1976; 29/11/1976; 30/11/1976
    - Nhep Pav, N/A (Reel 88, Frame 39)
    - Nhep Seth, N/A (Reel 83, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/11/1977; 27/11/1977
    - Nhep Sourng, N/A (Reel 87, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/11/1976; 13/11/1976(3); 12/11/1976; 30/10/1976; 6/11/1976; 8/11/1976; 1/11/1976; 19/12/1976(3); 16/11/1976(3); 26/11/1976; 28/11/1976; 23/11/1976; 3/11/1976; 15/11/1976; 25/11/1976; 21/11/1976
    - Nhep Thoeup, N/A (Reel 85, Frame 17)
    - Nhev Sarann, N/A (Reel 88, Frame 35)
    - Nhim Chhon, 20/3/1977 (Reel 86, Frame 3)
    - Nhim Mon, 17/2/1978 (Reel 89, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/2/1978; 19/3/1978
    - Nhim Sim, 26/9/1977 (Reel 86, Frame 24)
    - Nhim Sim, 13/6/1976 (Reel 88, Frame 10)
    - Nhim Soeurn, 4/2/1978 (Reel 83, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/2/1978; 27/2/1978
    - Nhim Sreang, 4/2/1977 (Reel 85, Frame 28)
    - Nhin Nat, 8/2/1978 (Reel 86, Frame 23)
    - Nhin Nhuom, 17/9/1977 (Reel 85, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/2/1977; 14/1/1978
    - Nhis Nhan, 7/3/1978 (Reel 85, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/3/1978
    - Nhoeung Hoeurn, 25/8/1977 (Reel 82, Frame 9)
    - Nhol Yim, N/A (Reel 85, Frame 3)
    - Nhom Saren, 28/4/1977 (Reel 88, Frame 47)
    - Nhoung Men, 14/7/1975 (Reel 86, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/22/1975
    - Nhov Doeun, N/A (Reel 86, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/10/1976(3); 4/10/1976; 1/10/1976; 10/10/1976; 12/10/1976; 6/10/1976; 7/10/1976; 5/10/1976; 12/10/1976; 9/10/1976; 11/10/1976
    - Nhy Ry, N/A (Reel 88, Frame 24)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/6/1977
    - Nil Lan, N/A (Reel 88, Frame 26)
    - Nim Heang, N/A (Reel 84, Frame 23)
    - Nim Ruoun, N/A (Reel 87, Frame 32)
    - Nin Sann, 7/2/1977 (Reel 84, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/3/1977; 1 section undated
    - Nin Yeath, 4/7/1977 (Reel 84, Frame 22)
    - Ninh Viet Hong, 13/9/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/10/1978
    - Nit Sun, N/A (Reel 89, Frame 17)
    - Nith Choeurn, 27/9/1977 (Reel 84, Frame 26)
    - Nith Leng, 6/1/1977 (Reel 87, Frame 5)
    - Nith Loch, N/A (Reel 84, Frame 18)
    - Nith Say, 17/9/1977 (Reel 84, Frame 17)
    - Nith Tha, N/A (Reel 85, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/10/1977
    - Nith Vy, N/A (Reel 88, Frame 16)
    - Noch Phon, 1/12/1978 (Reel 88, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/12/1978; 3/12/1978
    - Noem Nan, 6/1975 (Reel 86, Frame 11)
    - Noem Nay, 17/9/1977 (Reel 87, Frame 22)
    - Noeng Keo, 19/11/1975 (Reel 89, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/9/1975; 1 section undated
    - Noet Oeurng, N/A (Reel 83, Frame 7)
    - No'Ng Sam Oeurn, N/A (Reel 85, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/9/1976
    - Nong Sarim, N/A (Reel 87, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/6/1977; 25/6/1977; 26/6/1977; 26/6/1977; 12/7/1977; 5/7/1977
    - Nop Khav, 16/11/1978 (Reel 89, Frame 24)
    - Nop Khun, N/A (Reel 83, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/3/1977(2); 4/3/1977; 2/3/1977; 1/3/1977; 25/3/1977; 25/2/1977; 22/2/1977; 21/2/1977; 20/2/1977; 18/2/1977; 17/2/1977
    - Nop Nuon, 6/7/1977 (Reel 87, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/7/1977; 8/7/1977
    - Nop Ouch, 18/9/1975 (Reel 89, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/11/1975; 2 sections undated
    - Nop Pot, N/A (Reel 83, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/9/1975
    - Nop Samantara, 5/11/1977 (Reel 88, Frame 33)
    - Nop Soeun, 29/6/1977 (Reel 88, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/8/1977; 13/9/1977
    - Nop Sophal, 1/9/1976 (Reel 83, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/10/1976; 19/9/1976
    - Nop Soth, N/A (Reel 83, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/4/1977; 24/4/1977
    - Norn Nal, N/A (Reel 88, Frame 2)
    - Norng Chan, 28/8/1977 (Reel 87, Frame 11)
    - Norng Khem, N/A (Reel 85, Frame 11)
    - Norng Kiri, 28/10/1976 (Reel 85, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/11/1976
    - Nou Chhan, N/A (Reel 87, Frame 93)
    - Nou Chhun Ly, 12/8/1976 (Reel 88, Frame 36)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/9/1976(3)
    - Nou Chuon, 15/3/1978 (Reel 86, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/6/1978
    - Nou Dan, 30/7/1978 (Reel 87, Frame 29)
    - Nou Eang Leng, N/A (Reel 83, Frame 18)
    - Nou Nai Heat, 12/6/1978 (Reel 88, Frame 48)
    - Nou Nguon, 1/1/1977 (Reel 83, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/1/1977
    - Nou Ork, 28/1/1978 (Reel 82, Frame 1)
    - Nou Pech, 21/2/1978 (Reel 89, Frame 23)
    - Nou Pheap, 27/4/1975 (Reel 88, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/5/1975
    - Nou Pum, N/A (Reel 88, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/11/1975; 25/11/1975; 2 sections undated
    - Nou Sai Seam Pang, 30/6/1977 (Reel 86, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/9/1977; 11/8/1977
    - Nou Saman, N/A (Reel 83, Frame 19)
    - Nou Samoeurn, N/A (Reel 89, Frame 2)
    - Nou Saphal, 15/11/1976 (Reel 88, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/1/1977; 16/1/1977; 3 sections undated
    - Nou Savann, 4/2/1977 (Reel 83, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/2/1977; 28/2/1977
    - Nou Souloth, N/A (Reel 84, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/9/1977; 12/9/1977
    - Nou Vun, N/A (Reel 87, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/7/1977
    - Nou Yay, 27/11/1975 (Reel 89, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/2/1978; 11/12/1975
    - Noun Eam, 25/10/1977 (Reel 86, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/11/1977; 3/2/1978(2)
    - Nuan Van, 28/3/1977 (Reel 88, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/3/1977
    - Nuan Yum, 16/10/1975 (Reel 88, Frame 50)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/11/1975; 28/11/1975
    - Nui Lun, N/A (Reel 84, Frame 3)
    - Nun Bun Lim, N/A (Reel 86, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/1/1977; 1 section undated
    - Nun Thun, 8/1977 (Reel 84, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/9/1977; 21/10/1977
    - Nuoan Oeurn, N/A (Reel 85, Frame 18)
    - Nuon, N/A (Reel 87, Frame 37)
    - Nuon Cheth, 11/1/1977 (Reel 81, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/2/1977; 28/2/1977; 14/3/1977
    - Nuon Chhen, N/A (Reel 84, Frame 12)
    - Nuon Heath, 3/10/1977 (Reel 84, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/11/1977
    - Nuon Huy, 5/12/1978 (Reel 83, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/12/1978; 9/12/1978
    - Nuon Khun, N/A (Reel 89, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/1/1977
    - Nuon Khuth, 22/5/1975 (Reel 89, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/4/1975; 26/4/1975(2); 13/5/1975; 17/5/1975(2); 22/5/1975(3); 23/5/1975; 24/5/1975(6); 25/5/1975; 27/5/1975(2)
      28/8/1975; 1 section undated
    - Nuon Lauch, 30/7/1977 (Reel 84, Frame 16)
    - Nuon Man, 3/4/1976 (Reel 87, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/4/1976
    - Nuon Meas, 24/1/1977 (Reel 84, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/2/1977; 8/2/1977; 9/2/1977; 1/2/1977
    - Nuon Moeurn, 27/3/1977 (Reel 84, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/5/1977; 29/4/1977; 5/4/1977
    - Nuon Nin, N/A (Reel 85, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/9/1976; 8/9/1976(2); 9/9/1976(3); 9/10/1976
    - Nuon Phal, N/A (Reel 84, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/6/1978
    - Nuon Pho, 1/4/1978 (Reel 88, Frame 29)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/9/1978
    - Nuon Phon, 3/1977 (Reel 87, Frame 30)
    - Nuon Roeun, 11/5/1978 (Reel 86, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/5/1978
    - Nuon Roeurn, 1/10/1977 (Reel 84, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/11/1977; 15/1/1978
    - Nuon Seap, N/A (Reel 87, Frame 36)
    - Nuon Srean, 26/1/1978 (Reel 87, Frame 26)
    - Nuon Srey, N/A (Reel 84, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/4/1975
    - Nuon Srun, N/A (Reel 86, Frame 27)
    - Nut Heang, 5/1977 (Reel 84, Frame 11)
    - Nut Khoeurn, 30/7/1977 (Reel 82, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/9/1977; 8/8/1977
    - Nut Sak, N/A (Reel 81, Frame 1)
    - Nut Sarin, N/A (Reel 82, Frame 7)
    - Nuth Bun Song, 12/11/1977 (Reel 89, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/1/1978
    - Nuth Kap, 21/11/1978 (Reel 87, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/11/1978; 1/12/1978; 30/12/1978; 2 sections undated
    - Nuth Peourn, 24/2/1977 (Reel 85, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/3/1977; 21/3/1977
    - Nuth Savoeurn, N/A (Reel 89, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/1/1979
    - Nuth Voeun, 13/1/1976 (Reel 87, Frame 21)
    - Ny Mao, 5/6/1976 (Reel 84, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/8/1978
    - Ny Muong, 5/4/1978 (Reel 85, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/4/1978(2); 1 section undated
    - Ny Nim, 1/1978 (Reel 88, Frame 8)
- Series III: Confessions O-T
  - Names: O
    - Oeur Eap, 28/1/1978 (Reel 104, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/4/1978
    - Oeur Moch, N/A (Reel 91, Frame 10)
    - Oeur Moch, 25/10/1977 (Reel 105, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/3/1978
    - Oeur Samnom, 30/2/1977 (Reel 104, Frame 8)
    - Oeurn, 5/3/1977 (Reel 92, Frame 12)
    - Oeurn Moeurn, 9/10/1977 (Reel 105, Frame 13)
    - Oeurn Thuom, 15/6/1978 (Reel 105, Frame 20)
    - Oeurng Huy You, 31/8/1976 (Reel 91, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/9/1976; 11/9/1976; 10/9/1976; 9/1976; 18/9/1976
    - Ok Phoeurn, N/A (Reel 89, Frame 32)
    - Ol, N/A (Reel 89, Frame 33)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/2/1977; 27/2/1977; 1 section undated
    - Om Borey, 7/1977 (Reel 92, Frame 8)
    - Om Chor, N/A (Reel 90, Frame 12)
    - Om Prean, 3/12/1975 (Reel 104, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/12/1975
    - Om Sarin, 2/8/1975 (Reel 92, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/9/1975
    - Om Sek, N/A (Reel 91, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/2/1977; 8/1/1977; 6/2/1977; 17/12/1976; 21/12/1976; 25/12/1976; 21/12/1976; 17/12/1976
      3/1/1976; 25/12/1976; 16/1/1977; 20/1/1977; 5/1/1977; 2/2/1977
    - Om Tha, 17/10/1976 (Reel 105, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/2/1977; 12/11/1976; 13/11/1976
    - On Soeurn, 11/12/1976 (Reel 105, Frame 14)
    - On Yath, N/A (Reel 104, Frame 17)
    - Ong Ambok, 15/9/1977 (Reel 56, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/11/1977
    - Ong Bel, 10/11/1976 (Reel 89, Frame 34)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/11/1976(3); 20/11/1976; 20/12/1976; 25/12/1976; 5/1/1977(3); 28/12/1976; 5/1/1977; 6/1/1977
    - Ong Bith, 26/12/1976 (Reel 90, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/1/1977; 17/1/1977
    - Ong Chay, 15/1/1977 (Reel 92, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/3/1977(2); 11/3/1977(5); 12/3/1977(4); 28/2/1977
    - Ong Deth, N/A (Reel 105, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/9/1976; 5/9/1976; 8/9/1976; 6 sections undated
    - Ong Dul, 10/2/1978 (Reel 90, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/2/1978; 13/2/1978; 23/2/1978
    - Ong Lay San, N/A (Reel 89, Frame 35)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/11/1976; 27/16/1976; 28/11/1976;5/12/1976; 9/12/1976; 13/12/1976; 17/12/1976; 19/12/1976; 1 section undated
    - Ong Ol, 10/12/1978 (Reel 104, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/12/1978
    - Ong San, N/A (Reel 104, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/10/1976; 7/10/1976; 9/10/1976
    - Ong Sarin, N/A (Reel 90, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/10/1976; 10/10/1976; 12/10/1976; 13/10/1976(2); 14/10/1976(2); 15/10/1976(3); 11/10/1976(2); 25/10/1976; 27/10/1976
      5/11/1976; 6/11/1976(5); 7/11/1976(2); 20/11/1976
    - Ong Veng, N/A (Reel 105, Frame 17)
    - Ong Vorn, 26/8/1975 (Reel 92, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/9/1975
    - Onn, N/A (Reel 104, Frame 4)
    - Or Chheang, N/A (Reel 89, Frame 30)
    - Or Chy, 2/7/1977 (Reel 89, Frame 29)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/8/1976(2); 18/8/1976; 11/8/1976; 19/8/1976; 20/8/1976; 14/8/1976; 21/8/1976; 22/8/1976; 24/8/1976(4); 25/8/1976(4)
      26/8/1976(6); 27/8/1976(3); 8/8/1976; 8/9/1976; 28/3/1977; 5 sections undated
    - Or Kang, 18/1/1977 (Reel 104, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/1/1977(3); 1/2/1977; 30/1/1977(7); 2/2/1977(4); 19/5/1977; 23/2/1977(4)
    - Or Kim Choeu, N/A (Reel 105, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/2/1977; 26/2/1977
    - Or Makara, 23/7/1977 (Reel 92, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/9/1977; 3/10/1977
    - Or Malis, 1/8/1977 (Reel 92, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/11/1977; 4/10/1977
    - Or Ny, N/A (Reel 91, Frame 8)
    - Or Suy Leap, 9/2/1978 (Reel 105, Frame 29)
    - Or Voeurn, 19/4/1976 (Reel 105, Frame 2)
    - Ork Aum, 17/4/1978 (Reel 104, Frame 14)
    - Ork Hoeurn, 18/12/1977 (Reel 89, Frame 31)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/1/1978; 25/2/1978
    - Ork Horn, 28/6/1977 (Reel 92, Frame 5)
    - Ork Roun, 29/1/1978 (Reel 104, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/2/1978; 9/3/1978
    - Orl On, 20/8/1977 (Reel 104, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/11/1978
    - Orn Ban, 19/8/1977 (Reel 105, Frame 24)
    - Orrng Kim Yin, 2/8/1978/ (Reel 104, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/4/1978; 23/4/1978
    - Ou Chea, N/A (Reel 90, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/3/1978
    - Ou Chea, 3/6/1976 (Reel 104, Frame 12)
    - Ou Chhon, N/A (Reel 104, Frame 5)
    - Ou Eng Lang, 1/3/1977 (Reel 90, Frame 5)
    - Ou Kech, 19/8/1977 (Reel 104, Frame 11)
    - Ou Lam, 23/10/1976 (Reel 90, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/12/1976; 4//1/1977; 5/1/1977(2); 7/1/1977; 10/1/1977; 19/1/1977; 23/1/1977; 30/1/1977
    - Ou Marady, 14/7/1975 (Reel 92, Frame 30)
    - Ou Nget, 25/8/1977 (Reel 90, Frame 7)
    - Ou Noeun, 21/1/1977 (Reel 92, Frame 31)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/2/1977; 16/2/1977; 14/2/1977; 13/2/1977; 18/2/1977
    - Ou Phan, N/A (Reel 90, Frame 9)
    - Ou Pin, N/A (Reel 92, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/5/1977; 3/6/1977; 27/5/1977; 15/6/1977; 9/6/1977; 3 section undated
    - Ou Ream, 27/7/1978 (Reel 90, Frame 10)
    - Ou Ros, 17/6/1978 (Reel 105, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/6/1978
    - Ou Sar, 26/1/1976 (Reel 92, Frame 16)
    - Ou Seang, 12/9/1977 (Reel 90, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/1/1978; 6/2/1978; 25/2/1978
    - Ou Sou Meng, N/A (Reel 105, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/7/1977
    - Ou Vindy, N/A (Reel 104, Frame 22)
    - Ouch Ath, 13/1/1978 (Reel 104, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/1/1978; 11/2/1978; 3/3/1978
    - Ouch Chanthol, 7/1976 (Reel 104, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/5/1976
    - Ouch Orn, 24/7/1977 (Reel 92, Frame 11)
    - Ouch Touch, 1/9/1977 (Reel 92, Frame 13)
    - Ouk Chan Say, N/A (Reel 92, Frame 23)
    - Ouk Chhat, 28/1/1978 (Reel 104, Frame 24)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/1/1978; 19/2/1978; 14/4/1978; 2/5/1978; 3 sections undated
    - Ouk Chhoeung, 6/1977 (Reel 104, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/9/1977; 31/8/1977; 2/10/1977
    - Ouk Chy, 25/2/1976 (Reel 90, Frame 21)
    - Ouk Heang, 1/11/1975 (Reel 92, Frame 4)
    - Ouk Khorn, 4/4/1976 (Reel 104, Frame 20)
    - Ouk Muon, 4/3/1978 (Reel 91, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/3/1978; 8/3/1978
    - Ouk Mut, N/A (Reel 105, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/10/92
    - Ouk Nay, 12/4/1976 (Reel 105, Frame 8)
    - Ouk Ng, N/A (Reel 90, Frame 17)
    - Ouk On, N/A (Reel 105, Frame 3)
    - Ouk Pendara, N/A (Reel 90, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/2/1978; 26/12/1977
    - Ouk Phaly, 23/11/1977 (Reel 90, Frame 18)
    - Ouk Pheng, N/A (Reel 105, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/9/1976; 20/9/1976
    - Ouk Saem, N/A (Reel 92, Frame 17)
    - Ouk Saheang, N/A (Reel 105, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/11/1976
    - Ouk Sam At, N/A (Reel 104, Frame 21)
    - Ouk Sam Ourk, 6/7/1977 (Reel 92, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/9/1977; 18/10/1977
    - Ouk Samoeurn, 27/11/1976 (Reel 90, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/1/1977; 26/1/1977; 28/1/1977; 29/1/1977; 6/2/1977; 8/2/1977; 1/3/1977; 8/12/1976; 12/12/1976
      22/12/1976; 3 sections undated
    - Ouk Sath, N/A (Reel 90, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/3/1978
    - Ouk Savan, 24/5/1978 (Reel 104, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/7/1978; 12/7/1978
    - Ouk Savann, 3/2/1978 (Reel 92, Frame 24)
    - Ouk Savann, N/A (Reel 105, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/4/1978; 15/5/1978; 3 sections undated
    - Ouk Savon, 7/1977 (Reel 90, Frame 22)
    - Ouk Sen, 7/8/1978 (Reel 105, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/7/1978; 15/8/1978
    - Ouk Sok, 12/12/1976 (Reel 91, Frame 9)
    - Ouk Som Mary, 18/8/1977 (Reel 90, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/9/1977; 7/10/1977; 1 section undated
    - Ouk Sophal, N/A (Reel 90, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/7/1976; 14/7/1976(2); 2/8/1976; 21/8/1976; 27/7/1976; 28/8/1976
    - Ouk Sophan, 26/6/1977 (Reel 92, Frame 3)
    - Ouk Tem, N/A (Reel 92, Frame 7)
    - Ouk Tha, N/A (Reel 104, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 1977; 8/2/1977
    - Ouk Thear, 8/1977 (Reel 92, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/11/1977; 7/9/1977
    - Ouk Van, 1/6/1977 (Reel 90, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/9/1977
    - Ouk Yeoun, 7/1977 (Reel 90, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/9/1977; 23/10/1977
    - Ouk Yin, 1/8/1976 (Reel 104, Frame 19)
    - Oul Ham, 3/7/1977 (Reel 91, Frame 12)
    - Oul Van, 19/9/1975 (Reel 92, Frame 29)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/10/1992
    - Oum Chhan, 2/8/1978 (Reel 105, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/8/92
    - Oum Ean, 4/11/1976 (Reel 91, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/3/1977; 17/3/1977; 18/3/1977; 21/2/1977(2); 22/2/1977; 20/3/1977; 12/3/1977
    - Oum En, N/A (Reel 91, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/5/1977; 29/4/1977
    - Oum Kan, 8/1977 (Reel 105, Frame 7)
    - Oum Mol, N/A (Reel 92, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/12/1976; 3/1/1977; 11/1/1977(8); 15/12/1976(3); 23/12/1976(3); 16/12/1976
    - Oum Ol, N/A (Reel 105, Frame 18)
    - Oum Pha, N/A (Reel 90, Frame 25)
    - Oum Phat, N/A (Reel 105, Frame 12)
    - Oum Phy, N/A (Reel 92, Frame 14)
    - Oum Run, 9/10/1978 (Reel 90, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/10/1978
    - Oum Sam Nang, 21/11/1976 (Reel 91, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/1/1977; 6/1/1977; 9/1/1977; 7/12/1976; 9/12/1976; 10/12/1976; 11/12/1976; 28/11/1976
    - Oum Soeurn, N/A (Reel 90, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/9/1975; 19 sections undated
    - Oum Thim, N/A (Reel 91, Frame 2)
    - Oum Toy, 27/6/1977 (Reel 91, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/8/1977; 2 sections undated
    - Oun Chamroeun, N/A (Reel 104, Frame 2)
      Age: 11
      Dates of Confessions: 2/1/1977
    - Oun Chan, 22/9/1977 (Reel 92, Frame 19)
    - Oun Chhon, N/A (Reel 105, Frame 27)
    - Oun Horn On Yath, 23/4/1976 (Reel 104, Frame 16)
    - Oun Im, N/A (Reel 92, Frame 15)
    - Oun Mann, 10/1/1977 (Reel 90, Frame 27)
    - Oun Oeurn, 8/8/1976 (Reel 91, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/9/1977; 4/9/1976; 5/9/1976; 7/9/1976; 5/9/1976; 4/9/1976; 6/9/1976; 6/9/1976; 5/9/1976; 5/9/1976; 5/9/1976; 4/9/1976
      4/9/1976; 4/9/1976; 2 sections undated
    - Oun Phlak, N/A (Reel 105, Frame 26)
    - Oun Ran, 10/9/1977 (Reel 92, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/9/1977
    - Oun Sam Oeurn, N/A (Reel 92, Frame 9)
    - Oun Sam Oeurn, 8/1977 (Reel 105, Frame 11)
    - Oun Seng, N/A (Reel 91, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/9/1975
    - Oung Lany, N/A (Reel 181, Frame 20)
    - Ourn Lun, N/A (Reel 90, Frame 24)
    - Ourng Sophat, N/A (Reel 92, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/9/1975; 19/12/1975; 1 section undated
    - Oy Nguon Ly, N/A (Reel 92, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/7/1977; 1 section undated
  - Names: P
    - Pa Chhan, N/A (Reel 107, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/9/1975
    - Pa Onh, N/A (Reel 106, Frame 4)
    - Pa Phal, 21/2/1977 (Reel 110, Frame 11)
    - Pa Phan, 2/1978 (Reel 110, Frame 10)
    - Pach Sony, N/A (Reel 123, Frame 13)
    - Paen Mut, 20/5/1978 (Reel 107, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/6/1978; 3/6/1978(2)
    - Paing, N/A (Reel 123, Frame 31)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/4/1977
    - Pak Khna, 3/2/1978 (Reel 124, Frame 21)
    - Pak Ponn, N/A (Reel 123, Frame 27)
    - Pak Randy, 5/1/1976 (Reel 124, Frame 16)
    - Pak Rin, 6/1977 (Reel 116, Frame 17)
    - Pak Ruom, 16/10/1975 (Reel 121, Frame 5)
    - Pak Savann, N/A (Reel 122, Frame 4)
    - Pak Suon, N/A (Reel 124, Frame 11)
    - Pal Kroeurn, N/A (Reel 109, Frame 2)